♪♪♪
ONE TIME, ON TWITER
I HEARD ARIANA WAS PREGNANT
SO I GOT PREGNANT SO WE
COULD BE PREGNANT AT THE SAME
TURNS OUT IT WAS
JUST A RUMOR
ARIANA GRANDE TOLD ME MY HAIR
LOOKS SEXY PUSHED BACK
SHE'S NOT WRONG
ARIANA BROKE OFF AN ENGAGEMENT
SO I FOUND A GUY
TO PROPOSE TO ME
AND I BROKE OFF
AN ENGAGEMENT
I HEARD SHE'S A LESBIAN NOW
AND DATING SOME
CHICK CALLED AUBREY
IT'S FUCKING SICK
I HEARD THAT IF YOU
RECORD HER SNORING
AND PLAY IT BACKWARDS
IT SOUNDS LIKE FANTASIA
ARIANA SAYS HONEST
TO GOD KNOCK ME OUT
SO I DECIDED TO PUNCH
MYSELF IN THE FACE
IT WAS AWESOME
♪ THOUGHT I'D END
UP WITH SEAN ♪
♪ BUT HE WASN'T A MATCH ♪
♪ WROTE SOME
SONGS ABOUT RICKY ♪
♪ NOW I LISTEN AND LAUGH ♪
♪ EVEN ALMOST GOT MARRIED ♪
♪ AND FOR PETE,
I'M SO THANKFUL ♪
♪ WISH I COULD SAY,
"THANK YOU" TO MALCOLM ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE WAS AN ANGEL ♪
♪ ONE TAUGHT ME LOVE ♪
♪ ONE TAUGHT ME PATIENCE ♪
♪ AND ONE TAUGHT ME PAIN ♪
♪ NOW, I'M SO AMAZING ♪
♪ SAY I'VE LOVED
AND I'VE LOST ♪
♪ BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT I SEE ♪
♪ SO, LOOK WHAT I GOT ♪
♪ LOOK WHAT YOU TAUGHT ME ♪
♪ AND FOR THAT, I SAY ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT (NEXT) ♪
♪ THANK YOU,
NEXT (NEXT) ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'
GRATEFUL FOR MY EX ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT (NEXT) ♪
♪ THANK YOU,
NEXT (NEXT) ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT (NEXT) ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'... ♪
♪ SPEND MORE TIME
WITH MY FRIENDS ♪
♪ I AIN'T WORRIED
'BOUT NOTHIN' ♪
♪ PLUS, I MET SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ WE HAVIN' BETTER DISCUSSIONS ♪
♪ I KNOW THEY SAY I
MOVE ON TOO FAST ♪
♪ BUT THIS ONE GON' LAST ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HER NAME IS ARI ♪
♪ AND I'M SO GOOD WITH
THAT (SO GOOD WITH THAT) ♪
♪ SHE TAUGHT ME LOVE (LOVE) ♪
♪ SHE TAUGHT ME
PATIENCE (PATIENCE) ♪
♪ HOW SHE HANDLES PAIN (PAIN) ♪
♪ THAT SHIT'S AMAZING
(YEAH, SHE'S AMAZING) ♪
♪ I'VE LOVED AND I'VE
LOST (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT
I SEE (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ 'CAUSE LOOK WHAT
I'VE FOUND (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED FOR SEARCHING,
AND FOR THAT, I SAY ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT
(THANK YOU, NEXT) ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'
GRATEFUL FOR MY EX ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT
(THANK YOU, NEXT) ♪
(SAID THANK YOU, NEXT) ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT (NEXT) ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'
GRATEFUL FOR MY EX ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'... ♪
♪ ONE DAY I'LL WALK
DOWN THE AISLE ♪
♪ HOLDING HANDS
WITH MY MAMA ♪
♪ I'LL BE THANKING MY DAD ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SHE GREW
FROM THE DRAMA ♪
♪ ONLY WANNA DO
IT ONCE, REAL BAD ♪
♪ GON' MAKE THAT SHIT LAST ♪
♪ GOD FORBID
SOMETHING HAPPENS ♪
♪ LEAST THIS SONG IS A
SMASH (SONG IS A SMASH) ♪
♪ I'VE GOT SO
MUCH LOVE (LOVE) ♪
♪ GOT SO MUCH
PATIENCE (PATIENCE) ♪
♪ I'VE LEARNED
FROM THE PAIN (PAIN) ♪
♪ I TURNED OUT AMAZING
(TURNED OUT AMAZING) ♪
♪ SAY I'VE LOVED AND
I'VE LOST (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT
I SEE (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ 'CAUSE LOOK WHAT
I'VE FOUND (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED FOR SEARCHING ♪
♪ AND FOR THAT, I SAY ♪
I MEAN, HE WAS
REALLY CUTE YA KNOW
REALLY CUTE
AND IT WAS, IT WAS
REALLY BIG
HM
WELL I'VE ONLY GONE
OUT WITH ONE GUY THAT
HAD A BIG FRONT TOOTH AND
I LIKED IT 'CAUSE HE
NEVER GOT ANYTHING
STUCK IN THE FRONT TEETH
HM
BUT, HAVE YOU EVER GONE
OUT WITH SOMEONE THAT
HAD NO TEETH AT ALL?
NO
♪ IVE GOT SO MUCH LOVE
GOT SO MUCH PATIENCE ♪
♪ LEARNT FROM THE PAIN ♪
♪ TURNED OUT AMAZING ♪
♪ SAY I'VE LOVED AND I'VE LOST
(YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT I
SEE (YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ 'CAUSE LOOK WHAT I'VE FOUND
(YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ AIN'T NO NEED FOR
SEARCHING ♪
♪ AND FOR THAT, I SAY ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT
(THANK YOU, NEXT) ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'
GRATEFUL FOR MY EX ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT
(THANK YOU, NEXT) ♪
(SAID THANK YOU, NEXT) ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'
GRATEFUL FOR MY EX ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT ♪
♪ I'M SO FUCKIN'
GRATEFUL FOR MY EX ♪
♪ THANK YOU, NEXT ♪
♪ YEAH, YEE ♪
♪ ♪